Subject Files
Marist Archives and Special Collections
- Subject Files, 2.1.4.3
  - Subject files: 35 millimeter negative roll [softball], circa 1930s; 3 (Box 1581)
    - [Lowell Thomas and a woman at a softball game], 18
    - [Pitcher at a softball game], 19
    - [Pitcher and fieldsmen at softball game], 20
    - [Woman speaking to softball players at a game], 21
    - [Lowell Thomas pointing something out to a man], 22
    - [Woman signing autographs at a softball game], 23
    - [Spectators at a softball game], 24
    - [Lowell Thomas among a group of men at a softball game], 25
    - [Mens moking at a softball game], 26
    - [Man at a softball game], 27
  - Subject files: 35 millimeter negative roll [softball], circa 1930s; 4 (Box 1581)
    - [Spectators at a softball game], 1
    - [Spectators at a softball game], 2
    - [Softball players in the field], 3
    - [Softball player trying to catch a ball], 4
    - [Spectators at a softball game], 5
    - [Softball players in the field], 6
    - [Softball game], 7
    - [Softball game], 8
    - [Lowell Thomas pitching at a softball game], 9
    - [Two men sitting on a bench, overlooking a field], 10
    - [People at a softball BBQ], 11
    - [Guitar player and accordion player on a wooden stage at a softball BBQ], 12
    - [People at the softball BBQ], 13
    - [Guitar player and accordion player on a wooden stage at a softball BBQ], 14
    - [People at a softball BBQ], 15
    - [Softball BBQ], 16
    - [Softball BBQ], 17
    - [Lowell Thomas speaking to someone], 18
    - [Table at the softball BBQ], 19
    - [Lowell Thomas sitting at a table at the softball BBQ], 20
    - [Table at the softball BBQ], 21
    - [Bonfire at a softball BBQ], 22
    - [Cooks at a softball BBQ], 23
    - [Cooks at a softball BBQ], 24
  - Subject files: 35 millimeter negative roll [swimming], circa 1930s; 5 (Box 1581)
    - [Yard], 1
    - [Side of house], 2
    - [Church], 3
    - [Church], 4
    - [Church], 5
    - [Francis Ryan Thomas at the lake], 6
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. Diving], 7
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. Diving], 8
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. Diving], 9
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. Diving], 10
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. Diving], 11
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. Diving], 12
    - [Lowell Thomas diving], 13
    - [Lowell Thomas diving], 14
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. about to dive], 15
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. swimming], 16
    - [Lowell Thomas at the lake], 17
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. at the lake], 18
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. jumping into the lake], 19
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. jumping into the lake], 20
    - [Lowell Thomas, Frances Ryan Thomas, and two other sitting outside], 21
  - Subject files: 35 millimeter negative roll [Lowell Thomas, Jr. in uniform], circa 1940s; 6 (Box 1581)
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. outside with baby], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. holding a baby outside], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. holding a baby outside], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. and baby outside], 4
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. outside with baby], 5
    - [Lowell Thomas holding a baby outside], 6
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr., Frances Ryan Thomas and their dog], 7
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. and Frances Ryan Thomas], 8
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr., Frances Ryan Thomas and their dog], 9
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr., Frances Ryan Thomas and their dog], 10
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr., Frances Ryan Thomas and their dog], 11
    - [LowellT homas Jr. with baby outside], 12
    - [Lowell Thomas and woman with baby], 13
    - [Woman holding baby], 14
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr., Frances Ryan Thomas, and Lowell Thomas outside on the porch], 15
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr., Frances Ryan Thomas, and Lowell Thomas outside on the porch], 16
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas and Lowell Thomas on the porch], 17
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. posing on the porch], 18
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. in uniform], 19
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. and his dog], 20
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. and his dog], 21
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. posing on the porch with his dog], 22
    - [Lowell Thomas standing on porch, hands in his pockets], 23
  - Subject files: 35 millimeter negative roll [skiing], undated; 7 (Box 1581)
    - [People on skis going up the bunny hill], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas with others on skis], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas with other skiers], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas and other skiiers stand in a group], 4
    - [Ski slopes], 5
    - [Car in the driveway, snow piled up high], 6
  - Subject files: 35 millimeter negative roll [miscellaneous photographs], undated; 8 (Box 1581)
    - [Two women cooking], 1
    - [Woman sitting on a bus], 2
    - [Man feeding a kitten], 3
    - [Kitten being fed by a man], 4
    - [Reflection of a man and a woman in a window], 5
    - [Reflection of a man and a woman in a window], 6
    - [People talking outside of a window], 7
    - [Man with bowtie], 8
    - [Man in suit], 9
    - [Two men and a woman looking at a journal [?]], 10
    - [Two men sitting outside], 11
    - [Man sitting outside], 12
  - Subject files: 35 millimeter negative roll [miscellaneous photographs], undated; 9 (Box 1581)
    - [Women talking with a few men], 1
    - [Woman talking with four men], 2
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas with a group of other people], 3
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas standing with others], 4
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas singing [?] with a group of people], 5
    - [Frances Ryan Thoms with a group of people on the front porch], 6
    - [Man and woman singing in the crowd], 7
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas with others], 8
    - [Group of people talking], 9
    - [Lowell Thomas photographing a group of people on the front porch], 10
    - [Lowell Thomas photographing a group of people on the front porch], 11
    - [Group of people talking on the front porch], 12
    - [Woman smiling], 13
    - [Two women talking to a man], 14
    - [Two women talking, man looking at the camera], 15
    - [Woman and men talking], 16
    - [Herbert Hoover], 17
    - [Group of people on the front porch], 18
    - [Woman talking with others on front porch], 19
    - [Man and woman smiling], 20
    - [Women and man on front porch], 21
    - [Man and woman on front porch with other people], 22
    - [Woman and man on front porch, others in background], 23
    - [Woman speaking with two men], 24
    - [Lowell Thomas], 25
    - [Lowell Thomas speaking with a man and woman], 26
    - [Lowell Thomas speaking to a man and woman], 27
    - [Lowell Thomas speaking with a man], 28
    - [Women talking to Herbert Hoover and another man], 29
    - [Women talking to Herbert Hoover and another man], 30
    - [A man speaking with Frances Ryan Thomas], 31
    - [A man speaking with people on the porch], 32
    - [Woman and man on porch], 33
    - [Woman sitting in a rocking chair], 34
    - [Woman sitting in rocking chair], 35
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. and Frances Ryan Thomas and two men at the base of a cliff], 36
    - [Lowell Thomas and Frances Ryan Thomas with two men at the base of a cliff], 37
  - Subject files: 35 millimeter negative roll [miscellaneous photographs], undated; 10 (Box 1581)
    - [View of cars on bridge from front seat], 1
    - [Woman sticking her tounge out], 2
    - [Man standing on city sidewalk], 3
    - [Woman sitting outside of a store], 4
    - [Boy sitting on his bed (three photos)], 5
    - [Boy sitting on his bed (three photos)], 6